A Guide to the Robertson family genealogical notes, compiled 2024
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Robertson family genealogical notes, compiled 2024
Library of Virginia
54278
.175 cubic feet (1 box).
Stephen J. Yarbrough
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Stephen J. Yarbrough, Lake Frederick, Virginia.
Scope and Content
Notes. Includes information on the descendants of William Robertson (d. 1708) of Henrico County, Virginia, and Scotland, including information on lines which settled in Albemarle, Alleghany, Bedford, Culpeper, Henrico, Nelson, and Orange Counties, and Charlottesville, Harrisonburg, Lexington, Newport News, Norfolk, Roanoke, Salem, and Staunton, Virginia; and California, Florida, Georgia, Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, Kentucky, Maryland, Michigan, Minnesota, Mississippi, Missouri, New York, North Carolina, Oklahoma, Tennessee, Texas, and West Virginia. Other surnames mentioned: Apperson, Belton, Boyce, Carpenter, Dodd, Early, Goodloe, Haynes, Humphrey, Jewell, Johnson, Manning, McAlexander, Mittag, O'Neill, Peters, Philips, Poindexter, Robinson, Trower, Walker, Webb, Weber, Wood, Woodbury, and Yarbrough.
Contents List
- Robertson family summary (Folder 1)
- Albert Louis Robertson (1897-1970) (Folder 2)
- John Cosby Robertson (1859-1924) (Folder 3)
- Archelaus Jonathan Robertson (1826-1864) (Folder 4)
- Cosby Minor Robertson (1803-1876) (Folder 5)
- Archelaus Jonathan Robertson (1782-1856) (Folder 6)
- John Robertson (1753-1842) (Folder 7)
- Thomas Robertson (d. 1786) (Folder 8)
- Thomas Robertson (1700-178?) (Folder 9)
- John Robertson (1670-1720) (Folder 10)
- William Robertson (d. 1708) (Folder 11)